[
  {
    "Question": "Number of bits used by the IPv6 address",
    "Options": [
      {
        "Option": "A. 32 bit"
      },
      {
        "Option": "B. 64 bit"
      },
      {
        "Option": "C. 128 bits"
      },
      {
        "Option": "D. 256 bit"
      }
    ],
    "Correct Answer": "C. 128 bits"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What technology is used to record cryptocurrency transactions?",
    "Options": [
      {
        "Option": "A. Digital Wallet"
      },
      {
        "Option": "B. Mining"
      },
      {
        "Option": "C. Blockchain"
      },
      {
        "Option": "D. Token"
      }
    ],
    "Correct Answer": "C. Blockchain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which tech buzzword is closely related to Artificial Intelligence (AI)?",
    "Options": [
      {
        "Option": "A. Virtual reality"
      },
      {
        "Option": "B. Machine learning"
      },
      {
        "Option": "C. Cryptocurrency"
      },
      {
        "Option": "D. Microservices"
      }
    ],
    "Correct Answer": "B. Machine Learning"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an important step towards the paperless concept?",
    "Options": [
      {
        "Option": "A. Doxing"
      },
      {
        "Option": "B. Digitizing"
      },
      {
        "Option": "C. Debugging"
      },
      {
        "Option": "D. Downloading"
      }
    ],
    "Correct Answer": "B. Digitizing"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What technology is used to make telephone calls over the Internet possible?",
    "Options": [
      {
        "Option": "A. Bluetooth"
      },
      {
        "Option": "B. Ethernet"
      },
      {
        "Option": "C. NFC"
      },
      {
        "Option": "D. VoIP"
      }
    ],
    "Correct Answer": "D. VoIP"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which one is the first search engine in internet?",
    "Options": [
      {
        "Option": "A. Google"
      },
      {
        "Option": "B. Archie"
      },
      {
        "Option": "C. Altavista"
      },
      {
        "Option": "D. WAIS"
      }
    ],
    "Correct Answer": "B. Archie"
  },
  {
    "Question": "First computer virus is known as",
    "Options": [
      {
        "Option": "A. Rabbit"
      },
      {
        "Option": "B. Creeper Virus"
      },
      {
        "Option": "C. Elk Cloner"
      },
      {
        "Option": "D. SCA Virus"
      }
    ],
    "Correct Answer": "B. Creeper Virus"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Firewall in computer is used for",
    "Options": [
      {
        "Option": "A. Data Transmission"
      },
      {
        "Option": "B. Security"
      },
      {
        "Option": "C. Authentication"
      },
      {
        "Option": "D. Monitoring"
      }
    ],
    "Correct Answer": "B. Security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A dual layer blue ray disk can store data upto",
    "Options": [
      {
        "Option": "A.  20 GB"
      },
      {
        "Option": "B.  35 GB"
      },
      {
        "Option": "C.  12 GB"
      },
      {
        "Option": "D. 50 GB"
      }
    ],
    "Correct Answer": "D. 50 GB"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Number of layers in the OSI (Open Systems Interconnection) Model",
    "Options": [
      {
        "Option": "A.  9"
      },
      {
        "Option": "B.  3"
      },
      {
        "Option": "C.  7"
      },
      {
        "Option": "D. 11"
      }
    ],
    "Correct Answer": "C. 7"
  },
  {
    "Question": "gif is an extension of",
    "Options": [
      {
        "Option": "A.  Image file"
      },
      {
        "Option": "B.  Video file"
      },
      {
        "Option": "C.  Audio file"
      },
      {
        "Option": "D. Word file"
      }
    ],
    "Correct Answer": "A. Image file"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Computer Hard Disk was first introduced in 1956 by",
    "Options": [
      {
        "Option": "A.  Dell"
      },
      {
        "Option": "B.  Apple"
      },
      {
        "Option": "C.  Microsoft"
      },
      {
        "Option": "D. IBM"
      }
    ],
    "Correct Answer": "D. IBM"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which computer program converts assembly language to machine language",
    "Options": [
      {
        "Option": "A. Interpreter"
      },
      {
        "Option": "C. Compiler"
      },
      {
        "Option": "C. Assembler"
      },
      {
        "Option": "D. Comparator"
      }
    ],
    "Correct Answer": "C. Assembler"
  },
  {
    "Question": "In which year '@' sign was first chosen for its use in an e-mail address",
    "Options": [
      {
        "Option": "A. 1976"
      },
      {
        "Option": "B. 1980"
      },
      {
        "Option": "C. 1977"
      },
      {
        "Option": "D. 1972"
      }
    ],
    "Correct Answer": "D. 1972"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which one is the latest one from PARAM SuperSeries computers",
    "Options": [
      {
        "Option": "A. PARAM Yuva II"
      },
      {
        "Option": "B. PARAM 10000"
      },
      {
        "Option": "C. PARAM Padma"
      },
      {
        "Option": "D. PARAMnet"
      }
    ],
    "Correct Answer": "A. PARAM Yuva II"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A folder in Windows computer can't be made with the name",
    "Options": [
      {
        "Option": "A. can"
      },
      {
        "Option": "B. con"
      },
      {
        "Option": "C. mak"
      },
      {
        "Option": "D. make"
      }
    ],
    "Correct Answer": "B. con"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the extension type of the Excel 2007 files",
    "Options": [
      {
        "Option": "A. .xls"
      },
      {
        "Option": "B. .xlsx"
      },
      {
        "Option": "C. .xsl"
      },
      {
        "Option": "D. None of the above"
      }
    ],
    "Correct Answer": "B. .xlsx"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The maximum number of rows supported by Excel 2003 spreadsheet is",
    "Options": [
      {
        "Option": "A. 10,000"
      },
      {
        "Option": "B. 35,356"
      },
      {
        "Option": "C. 55,782"
      },
      {
        "Option": "D. 65,536"
      }
    ],
    "Correct Answer": "D. 65,536"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is not one of the early 'protocols,' or ways to use the Internet?",
    "Options": [
      {
        "Option": "A. Blogging"
      },
      {
        "Option": "B. Telnet"
      },
      {
        "Option": "C. Gopher"
      },
      {
        "Option": "D. FTP"
      }
    ],
    "Correct Answer": "A. Blogging"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A network designed to allow communication within an organization is called:",
    "Options": [
      {
        "Option": "A. the World Wide Web"
      },
      {
        "Option": "B. Yahoo"
      },
      {
        "Option": "C. an intranet"
      },
      {
        "Option": "D. the Internet"
      }
    ],
    "Correct Answer": "C. an intranet"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the value of Pi to three decimal places?",
    "Options": [
      {
        "Option": "A. 3.141"
      },
      {
        "Option": "B. 3.142"
      },
      {
        "Option": "C. 3.1415"
      },
      {
        "Option": "D. 3.1409"
      }
    ],
    "Correct Answer": "C. 3.142"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What year did Apple launch the Macintosh 128K?",
    "Options": [
      {
        "Option": "A. 1983"
      },
      {
        "Option": "B. 1985"
      },
      {
        "Option": "C. 1977"
      },
      {
        "Option": "D. 1999"
      }
    ],
    "Correct Answer": "B. 1985"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Identify the range of byte data types in JavaScript.",
    "Options": [
      {
        "Option": "A. -10 to 9"
      },
      {
        "Option": "B. -128 to 127"
      },
      {
        "Option": "C. -32768 to 32767"
      },
      {
        "Option": "D. -2147483648 to 2147483647"
      }
    ],
    "Correct Answer": "B. -128 to 127"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is not a built-in module in NODE.js?",
    "Options": [
      {
        "Option": "A. fs"
      },
      {
        "Option": "B. http"
      },
      {
        "Option": "C. mysql"
      },
      {
        "Option": "D. path"
      }
    ],
    "Correct Answer": "C. mysql"
  },
  {
    "Question": "IPV4 Address is",
    "Options": [
      {
        "Option": "A. 8 bit"
      },
      {
        "Option": "B. 16 bit"
      },
      {
        "Option": "C. 32 bit"
      },
      {
        "Option": "D. 64 bit"
      }
    ],
    "Correct Answer": "C. 32 bit"
  },
  {
    "Question": "DNS is the abbreviation of",
    "Options": [
      {
        "Option": "A. Dynamic Name System"
      },
      {
        "Option": "B. Dynamic Network System"
      },
      {
        "Option": "C. Domain Name System"
      },
      {
        "Option": "D. Domain Network Service"
      }
    ],
    "Correct Answer": "C. Domain Name System"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which keys are used to switch between programs in Windows?",
    "Options": [
      {
        "Option": "A. Ctrl+TAB"
      },
      {
        "Option": "B. Alt+TAB"
      },
      {
        "Option": "C. Shift+TAB"
      },
      {
        "Option": "D. Shift+Enter"
      }
    ],
    "Correct Answer": "B. Alt+TAB"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What does the Internet prefix WWW stand for?",
    "Options": [
      {
        "Option": "A. Wide Width Wickets"
      },
      {
        "Option": "B. World Wide Web"
      },
      {
        "Option": "C. Worldwide Weather"
      },
      {
        "Option": "D. Western Washington World"
      }
    ],
    "Correct Answer": "B. World Wide Web"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A network designed to allow communication within an organization is called:",
    "Options": [
      {
        "Option": "A. the World Wide Web"
      },
      {
        "Option": "B. Yahoo"
      },
      {
        "Option": "C. an intranet"
      },
      {
        "Option": "D. the Internet"
      }
    ],
    "Correct Answer": "C. an intranet"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of these products is not made by the Apple Corporation?",
    "Options": [
      {
        "Option": "A. IMAX"
      },
      {
        "Option": "B. iPhone"
      },
      {
        "Option": "C. iMac"
      },
      {
        "Option": "D. iPod"
      }
    ],
    "Correct Answer": "A. IMAX"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of these is a file format for digital images?",
    "Options": [
      {
        "Option": "A. CIA"
      },
      {
        "Option": "B. JPG"
      },
      {
        "Option": "C. ICBM"
      },
      {
        "Option": "D. IBM"
      }
    ],
    "Correct Answer": "B. JPG"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How much did Steve Job's first computer go for at auction?",
    "Options": [
      {
        "Option": "A. $1.2 million"
      },
      {
        "Option": "B. $500,000"
      },
      {
        "Option": "C. $223,000"
      },
      {
        "Option": "D. $3.4 million"
      }
    ],
    "Correct Answer": "A. $1.2 million"
  },
  {
    "Question": "'.MOV' extension refers usually to what kind of file?",
    "Options": [
      {
        "Option": "A. Image file"
      },
      {
        "Option": "B. Animation/movie file"
      },
      {
        "Option": "C. Audio file"
      },
      {
        "Option": "D. MS Office document"
      }
    ],
    "Correct Answer": "B. Animation/movie file"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The brain of any computer system is",
    "Options": [
      {
        "Option": "A. ALU"
      },
      {
        "Option": "B. Memory"
      },
      {
        "Option": "C. CPU"
      },
      {
        "Option": "D. Control unit"
      }
    ],
    "Correct Answer": "C. CPU"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following computer languages is used for artificial intelligence?",
    "Options": [
      {
        "Option": "A. FORTRAN"
      },
      {
        "Option": "B. PROLOG"
      },
      {
        "Option": "C. COBOL"
      },
      {
        "Option": "D. C"
      }
    ],
    "Correct Answer": "B. PROLOG"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which was the first purely object-oriented programming language developed?",
    "Options": [
      {
        "Option": "A. Kotlin"
      },
      {
        "Option": "B. SmallTalk"
      },
      {
        "Option": "C. Java"
      },
      {
        "Option": "D. C++"
      }
    ],
    "Correct Answer": "B. SmallTalk"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the name of the organization that regulates the insurance industry in India?",
    "Options": [
      {"Option":"A. IRDAI"},
      {"Option":"B. IIB"},
      {"Option":"C. IR"},
      {"Option":"D. IOI"}
    ],
    "Correct Answer": "A. IRDAI"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the name of Sun Life Financial's wealth management division?",
    "Options": [
      {"Option":"A. Sun Life Wealth"},
      {"Option":"B. Sun Life Management"},
      {"Option":"C. Sun Life Financial Wealth"},
      {"Option":"D. Sun Life Capital"}
    ],
    "Correct Answer": "A. Sun Life Wealth"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What type of insurance protects businesses from financial losses due to employee dishonesty?",
    "Options": [
      {"Option": "A. Catastrophe"},
      {"Option":"B. Fidelity"},
      {"Option":"C. Cyber"},
      {"Option":"D. Key person"}
    ],
    "Correct Answer": "B. Fidelity"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the name of Sun Life Financial's corporate responsibility program?",
    "Options": [
      {"Option":"A. Brighter Life"},
      {"Option":"B. Brighter Day"},
      {"Option":"C. Bright Life"},
      {"Option":"D. Better Life"}
    ],
    "Correct Answer": "A. Brighter Life"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Process by which an insurance company sets the premium for any insurance policy?",
    "Options": [
      {"Option":"A. Pricing"},
      {"Option":"B. Risk Assessment"},
      {"Option":"C. Underwriting"},
      {"Option":"D. All of the above"}
    ],
    "Correct Answer": "C. Underwriting"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When was Sun Life Financial founded?",
    "Options": [
      {"Option":"A. 1865"},
      {"Option":"B. 1871"},
      {"Option":"C. 1842"},
      {"Option":"D. 1887"}
    ],
    "Correct Answer": "A. 1865"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Who is the managing director of Sun Life Financial?",
    "Options": [
      {"Option":"A. Tarun Sareen"},
      {"Option":"B. Ajayan Narayan"},
      {"Option":"C. Ajitpal Singh"},
      {"Option":"D. Chandan Barve"}
    ],
    "Correct Answer": "A. Tarun Sareen"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which Sun Life event won Ragan's award for virtual employee engagement?",
    "Options": [
      {"Option":"A. Sunny Life"},
      {"Option":"B. Sunny Summer"},
      {"Option":"C. SunVibe"},
      {"Option":"D. Sun days"}
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "B. Sunny Summer"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Who is the president of Sun Life Asia?",
    "Options": [
      {"Option":"A. Ingrid Johnson"},
      {"Option":"B. Laura Money"},
      {"Option":"C. Tom Murphy"},
      {"Option":"D. Helena Pagano"}
    ],
    "Correct Answer": "A. Ingrid Johnson"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What does the D stand for in BOLDER?",
    "Options": [
      {"Option":"A. Diversity"},
      {"Option":"B. Driving outcomes"},
      {"Option":"C. Driving results"},
      {"Option":"D. Draw outcomes"}
    ],
    "Correct Answer": "B. Driving outcomes"
  }
]